<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE resources [
	<!ENTITY nbsp "&#160;"><!-- non-breaking space, http://www.fileformat.info/info/unicode/char/00A0/index.htm -->
	<!ENTITY LI "\n&#8195;&#8226;&#8194;"><!-- m-space (\u2003) bullet (\u2022) n-space (\u2002) -->
	]>
<resources>
	<string name="about_faq"><b>What is this app?</b>
		\nThis is a home inventory application.
		It helps you maintain a list of stuff you have, with an efficient interface and easy navigation.

		\n\n<b>When is it useful?</b>
		&LI;You have a remote storage and you don\'t remember exactly what\'s there.
		&LI;You\'re moving, to remember which box contains what.
		&LI;You\'re tidy and organized and want to know where your stuff belongs.
		&LI;You want to inventory valuable items for insurance purposes.
		&LI;You\'re not at home, but your family member/flatmate wants something.
		&LI;You want to declutter, you can create a list of stuff you want to throw away.
		&LI;You\'re curious how many pens you have lying around the house.

		\n\n<b>How is the inventory structured?</b>
		\nThe inventory structure is based on real life.
		There are 3 types of belongings: <i>properties</i> have <i>rooms</i> or areas and <i>items</i> located within.
		Container items, like boxes, can contain any other items.
		You can create <i>lists</i> of items, just like you could on a piece of paper.
		See <i>Structure</i> section in Help for more details.

		\n\n<b>How can I enter multiple images for a single item?</b>
		\nThis is currently not directly possible,
		but as a workaround you can create items within that item and select the “<i>Extra Images</i>” category.
		Feel free to contact me if you feel it\'s an important feature for you.

		\n\n<b>How can I leave feedback? What is feedback?</b>
		\nTap on the link below the application name/version in the About section.
		Feel free to send any kind of comment, request, suggestion, error report;
		just about any thought regarding this app.
	</string>
	<string name="about_help"><big><b>Structure</b></big>
		\n\n<b>Properties</b>
		\nYour inventory, everything you own, must be located somewhere.
		In the app, these locations are called <i>properties</i>;
		they\'re usually buildings or land that you own or visit often.

		\n\n<b>Rooms</b>
		\nEach <i>property</i> has significant areas where stuff can be located.
		Most of the time these are <i>rooms</i> in your home.
		In this app, the term “<i>room</i>” encompasses
			areas that are not separated by walls (e.g. gardens),
			or entire buildings separate from the main house (e.g. garage, shed).
		\nIf you have a newly designed home or live in a studio apartment,
		the rooms may be areas of the main living space: for example
			your bed and its surroundings is the “bedroom”,
			or the kitchen counter, fridge, sink area is the “kitchen”.
		The choice is yours.

		\n\n<b>Items</b>
		\nAn item is a single piece of the stuff that you own.
		It\'s up to you how specific you want to be. An item could be
			your whole desktop computer with its peripherals (monitor, keyboard, printer)
			or a single cog or LEGO building block.
		Of course, you don\'t have to input every little piece, but the possibility is there.

		\n\n<b>Items (Hierarchy)</b>
		\nOne of the key features of this app is that <i>any</i> item could <i>contain</i> any number of other items,
		similar to Russian matryoshka nesting dolls.
		This nesting ability gives organisation and definition to your inventory.
		Each item is listed as having a particular location, which is calculated based on the hierarchy of items containing it.
		It\'s easy to locate everything quickly when needed: no more “<i>Was it in this or that box?</i>”.
		\nFor example a common layout of items in a wardrobe:
		&LI;there\'s stuff hanging in the main area
		&LI;there are shoes and boxes at the bottom
		&LI;there are possibly boxes on top of the wardrobe
		\nAll of these (main area, bottom, atop) can be represented as items in the <i>compartment</i> category.
		For example, imagine there\'s a squash ball inside it\'s packaging in that box at the bottom, the hierarchy of items are:
		(<i>Home</i> ► <i>Bedroom</i> ►) <i>Wardrobe</i> ► <i>Bottom</i> ► <i>Carton box</i> ► <i>Squash ball box</i> ► <i>Blue squash ball</i>.
		Remember, using compartments to organize items, and inputting the packaging are optional.

		\n\n<b>Items (Groups)</b>
		\nA group holds items together, but it\'s not an actual physical container.
		It is represented as a special category you can select for the item.
		It helps to make the item listing cleaner by giving headings to the contained items.
		A good example when groups are useful is inputting a pencil holder: you can
		separate pens and pencils into their own groups and leave the rest without a group (e.g. ruler and scissors).

		\n\n<b>Lists</b>
		\nYou can create <i>lists</i> for items you want to remember for any particular reason.
		Lists are virtual, because they don\'t contain the items they list, just reference them;
		think of them as notes on a sheet of paper.
		\nFor example if you go on summer vacation every year, you can create a list for all the items that you always bring,
		so when it\'s time to travel you can quickly gather everything and never forget anything anymore.
		Other examples are:
		&LI;a list for stuff you lent to someone,
		&LI;a list for stuff that you can\'t find,
		&LI;a list for broken stuff that needs replacing.
		
		\n\n\n<big><b>Interface</b></big>
		\nAll of the actions are available through the action bar on the top.
		Long tap an icon on the action bar to see what it does.
		There are also shortcuts to some of those actions detailed below.

		\n\n<b>Headers</b>
		\nWhen a belonging is opened, the top part of the screen shows its image along with its category.
		If the belonging doesn\'t have an image, the category\'s icon is used as a ghost image.
		Single tap on the image (if it exists) will show the image in a larger view.
		Tapping on a ghost image or long tapping on an existing image will initiate editing and changing the image. 
		Tapping the small icon in the lower right corner will always initiate changing the type of the belonging.
		Scrolling right on the header will give you more details about the belonging, for example location.

		\n\n<b>Grids</b>
		\nAll contents of the belongings are shown in a multi-column grid.
		This helps fast navigation and visual search.
		The grids adjust to the screen size, so if your device has a wide enough screen it\'ll be used efficiently.
		Each grid item shows the image of the belonging (if any),
			the name,
			the category in the lower right corner and
			the number items listed inside in the lower left corner.

		\n\n<b>Editing</b>
		\nEditing allows you to change the details of a belonging, like name, description, category and image.
		\n<i>Name</i>:
			This name will show up everywhere where the belonging is visible and can be used to search for it.
		\n<i>Description</i>:
			Additional details about the belonging, like serial number, purchase date, etc.
		\n<i>Image</i>:
			Tapping on the image will initiate changing the image.
			Long tapping on the image will remove the image.
		\n<i>Category</i>:
			After (and during) entering the name of a belonging you may get suggestions for categories.
			Tap a suggestion or choose from the dropdown to set the category.

		\n\n<b>Taking a Picture</b>
		\nIf your device supports it, the app has a built-in camera which helps with framing and cropping the item.
		If you prefer to use an external camera app, or you have an image that you wish to import, use the gallery icon.
		\nThe cropping selection is a rectangle laid out on top of the image.
		You can resize the selecting by dragging the 4 corners.
		You can move the selection by dragging the middle of it.
		The color of the cropping selection indicates the status of taking the picture:
		<!-- net.twisterrob.android.view.SelectionView.SelectionStatus -->
		&LI;<font color="cyan">blue</font> for camera active
		&LI;<font color="yellow">yellow</font> for work in progress
		&LI;<font color="green">green</font> for focused and ready
		&LI;<font color="red">red</font> for out of focus or error
		\n<b>To take a picture</b> using the built-in camera:
		&LI;if the image is still, press the middle picture button, to start the preview
		&LI;if the image is moving, press the middle picture button, to take a picture
		&LI;highlight the area you want to crop using the selection
		&LI;press the right crop button
		&LI;save the belonging
		\nAs a shortcut: pressing the crop button while the preview is showing will take the picture and immediately crop it.

		\n\n\n<big><b>Actions</b></big>

		\n\n<b>Single belongings</b>
		\nTo take any action on a single belonging, open it and check the available actions on the action bar.

		\n\n<b>Selection</b>
		\nTo take action on more than one item at once, you\'ll need to select them first.
		You can initiate a selection by long-tapping any item and then tapping any others you wish to select.
		The possible actions are available on the action bar.

		\n\n<b>Move</b>
		\nIf something has been relocated, you can track that by selecting the item and moving using the move action.
		For example if you\'re moving homes you can select all of the items in a drawer and move them to a box.
		After the moving is initiated, you can select where you want to move starting from the closest belonging.
		You can navigate up in the hierarchy using the back button (contrary to usual behavior) and the arrow in the upper left corner.
		Click “<i>OK</i>” to move to the current location; “<i>Cancel</i>” if you changed your mind.
		The target doesn\'t necessarily have to exist; you can create belongings on the fly while browsing.

		\n\n<b>Delete</b>
		\nDeleting any belonging will delete <i>all</i> of its contents as well.
		You\'ll be warned about this with a confirmation question.
		If you want to keep what\'s inside a belonging, move them first to somewhere else and then delete the empty belonging.

		\n\n\n<big><b>Sunburst Diagram</b></big>
		\nSunburst is an aid visualizing hierarchical data by showing everything on a single chart.
		The middle is the current location and everything around it (on concentric circles) is contained within.
		It shows you, for example, what the distribution of your items is within your inventory:
		the belonging with the most items will have the largest arc.
		\nYou can drill down into the diagram by tapping a belonging\'s segment.
		The current belonging can be opened from the action bar.
		If something has too many items and it distorts the diagram, you can exclude it from the action bar.
		For example, use this if you want to see where most of your stuff is other than in your own room.

		\n\n\n<big><b>Backup</b></big>
		\nYou can select a directory where you want to export the whole inventory and then press the “<i>Export</i>” button.
		You can use the same browser to find an existing inventory backup and import it by tapping on it.
	</string>
	<string name="about_tips">
		&LI;If you have a steady hand, you can use the <i>Crop</i> button to take an image and crop it immediately.
		&LI;If a belonging doesn\'t have an image, tap the ghost image to add a new image.
		&LI;Other than the basic shelves and drawers, create compartments for atop a cupboard, and in front of or below for stuff on the ground.
		&LI;Instead of deleting items you can create a “<i>Thrown Away</i>” room in a “<i>Virtual</i>” property and move stuff there.
		It also helps to create separate <i>Groups</i> in that room: “<i>Broken</i>”, “<i>Expired</i>”, “<i>Used up</i>”, “<i>Sold</i>”, “<i>Gave away</i>” to record the reason.
		&LI;Create an “<i>Original Packaging</i>” room in a “<i>Virtual</i>” property to record what was in the original boxes in case you want to re-sell stuff later.
		&LI;Put an exclamation mark (!) in front of a belonging\'s name to bring it to the top of the list.
		<!--&LI;In case your device doesn\'t have enough free space to export a backup use an USB stick with an OTG cable.-->
	</string>
</resources>
